Get away !
" We Are What We Are "
Mom 's looking for you .
Your father hasn 't come home .
You 're going to have to open up .
What are you waiting for ?
What about Sabina ?
Sabina will stay here and fix the clocks .
Cut it out !
is my watch ready ?
Good morning , could you tell me ...
Don 't tell me you don 't have it !
Your father promised it to me three weeks ago .
Could you tell me which one 's yours ?
It 's a gold Mido .
What are you laughing at , punk ?
Julian !
Sabina !
That 's the second time , kiddo .
Where 's your old man ?
He owes me for weeks . You 're way behind !
He won 't be long .
No , I think you 'd better take your shit and go !
Come on , asshole ! Go for it !
Pack up your shit or I 'll throw it out !
Now what ?
" Now what ? "
What do you mean ? What are we going to tell Mom ?
The truth . They kicked us out because Dad didn 't pay the bill .
No , they kicked us out because you 're always fighting !
Don 't defend him .
They kicked us out because he didn 't pay .
It was your fault .
They kicked us out because Dad spends all day with whores .
What are you doing here ?
What happened , Alfredo ?
We got kicked out of the market .
What ?
They changed managers . Someone else is fixing watches .
Julian come here !
- Now what ? - What happened ?
- l told you , Mom . - l 'm not asking you !
The damn woman went berserk !
What did you do ?
Nothing , we were working and she kicked us out .
- Right ! Just like that ! - Yes , just like that .
The only job your father can do
and you blow it !
We didn 't do anything .
Do you think I 'm dumb or what ?
Who took my key from the flower pot ?
They told me someone died at the mall ...
The man who looked at the mannequins .
Dad 's dead !
Damn his addiction to whores !
Those bitches killed him !
Bitches !
What are we going to do ?
Are we going to carry on ?
- We have to go on as usual . - We can 't go on without Dad .
Don 't talk bullshit !
We have to , Alfredo .
We have to get something for tomorrow .
What are we supposed to do ?
Mom locked herself up in her room .
Dad is lost .
Dead .
Dad is dead .
- How do you know ? - Didn 't you hear what I said ?
It could be anyone .
Did they confirm it ?
- Who ? - The people from the mall .
Who are they ? How do you know them ?
You 're out of it .
Remember who you 're talking to .
It can 't be .
We have to wait for him .
No , he 'd have been home by now .
You act like you 're glad .
- Shut up , asshole ! - You shut up , you stupid shit !
There 's nothing .
You 'd better find something .
From now on , it 's up to you .
Mom ... Are you ok ?
What shall we do ?
Mom ?
Whatever happens , we have to get something .
We have to go now .
We 've never done it in the daylight .
It can 't be that hard if he did it .
Don 't talk about Dad like that !
- Shut up , faggot ! - Stop it .
Let 's go to the corner .
- Mom won 't like that . - lt 's the easiest .
No . Too risky .
Why not go to the bridge ?
We have to get something by tomorrow .
Then we can figure out what to do .
What are you waiting for ?
You 're the one who has to do it .
Damn , Tito !
Over the years , you 've become a master !
Yeah , my technique 's improved .
Look ,
I 'm giving him texture , color , covering up the scar ...
You have to ... you know ?
You have to be a fucking artist .
But don 't put too much effort into this one .
We 're cremating him .
What ?
Fuck ! Why didn 't you tell me ?
I wouldn 't have made the asshole up so nice .
God rest his soul !
Nobody respects my work around here .
Why didn 't you tell me ? You ...
Why didn 't you tell me ?
Why did you send for us ?
I thought this would interest you .
What ?
A cold one ?
Not a cold one .
This guy came in from a mall .
He died of poisoning .
I did a spectacular job on him .
First-rate job .
Don 't you think ?
I performed an autopsy
and found something very interesting .
You 've no idea how many people come in here chewed up .
It 's shocking how many people eat each other in this city .
In the reports they blame the rats .
But it 's the two-legged kind .
" One night , a city rat ... "
Well , this old man isn 't going to be eating anyone else .
What good is he to us ?
You could investigate who he ate .
We don 't solve old cases .
What 's more , we don 't solve new ones either .
But this case will make us famous , make us rich !
Us ? Sounds like a crowd to me .
But thanks for the trinket .
All these assholes are the same .
They just go on forever .
- Wait . - What ?
We have to do something or we 're screwed .
Wait until it 's quieter .
No , we can 't wait .
You know what happens
if we don 't have someone by tomorrow ?
Julian !
- Help ! - Julian !
Let 's go ! Let 's go !
Get him ! Get him !
What happened ?
It 's Mom .
What did you do ?
We went to get someone .
What ?
Are you idiots ?
Your father dies and you go out hunting ?
You put the family at risk , Alfredo .
We did it for the ritual .
The ritual ?
What do you know about the ritual ?
If you knew so much , you 'd know what comes next .
We have to pick a leader .
That 's next .
Next we start shaking , because we 're going to die .
Do you know what Mom meant ?
We have to get something for tomorrow .
You 're the oldest , Alfredo .
You must take Dad 's place .
And if I don 't want to ?
It 's not about wanting .
You 're the most capable ...
the most sensitive ...
the most balanced .
I couldn 't even catch a kid .
According to what Dad taught us , you 're the next one .
You have to keep the ritual going
and lead the family .
I can 't .
You have to , Alfredo .
Mom loses her temper .
- She puts us at risk . - Mom always knows what to do .
Yeah ?
She 's still locked in her room .
We 're in real trouble and she does nothing .
Just scolds you all the time .
Alfredo , look at me .
Look at me !
No matter what , we have to continue .
And what should I do ?
Julian would be better .
Julian 's clumsy and violent .
Cheat ,
deceive people .
I can 't be the leader ,
but I can help you .
- Hunt down a whore . - What ?
You know Mom hates that .
- lt 's forbidden . - Forbidden ?
Dad used to do it , didn 't he ?
Mom can 't forbid us anything .
Now you 're the leader .
Get a whore .
We 'll dress her in my clothes to fool Mom .
Well ?
Tell Julian to come .
What 's up ?
Sabina says to go ...
From now on , you 're going to obey Alfredo .
You 'll get to eat a whore bite by bite ...
Just like Dad .
Let 's get a whore .
What ?
Not afraid of Mom anymore ?
No .
We must get someone by tomorrow .
Looking for me ?
- Who else ? - Yeah ?
- What 's the deal ? - Let 's go , ok ?
Let 's go .
No way , honey .
That 's more expensive .
When has money been a problem ?
It 's no problem for you , you 're loaded .
So let 's go .
No , let me go . Let me go .
Don 't be an asshole ! Let me go !
Julian , what are you doing ?
Hurry up !
Come on .
Leave her !
Let 's go , Julian !
Shut her up !
You 're such a loser !
What should I do ? Kill her ?
Calm down , Julian !
Cool it !
- What 's wrong with you , Julian ? - What do you mean ?
What do I mean ? There 's a whore in the trunk !
I 'm getting food for tomorrow .
Food ?
You beat the shit out of her in front of everyone .
At least they don 't die in my arms .
You think you 're really tough ?
I 'm not afraid of you .
You should be .
Sabina 's with Mom .
A whore ?
Who do you think you are ?
Who do you both think you are ?
- She 's not a whore ... - l 'm not an idiot .
So what if she is a whore ?
We have to prepare her .
If you scream again , I 'll tear your eyes out !
No ! Don 't kill me .
Please don 't hurt me !
You can rape me . You can both fuck me .
Do whatever you want to me .
Let me go .
So today 's your lucky day ?
Don 't play dumb .
Think I didn 't see the finger in the jar ?
The nutcases at the morgue gave it to you , right ?
You think they called you so you could solve the case ?
Think you 're the first ones those nuts called ?
They called everyone before you .
You 're just a fifth-rate cop .
And stop reading that file . You look ridiculous .
Do you have any idea what would happen
if we broke this case ?
The money we 'd make ?
We 'd even meet the President in his fight against crime .
You have a lot of courage to lead the family , no ?
- lt 's just that ... - You shut up !
Do you want to go whoring like Dad ?
Then you have to take me to your whores .
Meanwhile , we 'll see what our leader decides for us .
is being without Dad going to be like this ?
I think so .
Where 's Alfredo ?
Stop !
I 'm getting off !
Getting off !
Stop ! I told you I was getting off , you prick !
I was too hard on him .
It 's not good for him to be alone .
But now Alfredo wants to make all the decisions .
As if it mattered right now .
He 's trying to do something for us .
To help .
Help !
You think bringing whores home helps ?
It 's hard for him that Dad isn 't here .
He really loved him .
Alfredo isn 't the only one who loved him .
I loved him , too .
I have a lot more right than he does .
You were always complaining about Dad .
- As if you didn 't love him . - How can you say that ?
It 's true .
At least Alfredo does something .
Never say I don 't do anything for the family again !
Take out the whore 's body !
You 're paid for .
You always defended Alfredo ,
ever since he was little .
You 'd wrap yourselves in the oilcloth
and get under the table and say you were a taco .
Sabina would be left out .
You 'd say : You are the salsa .
And she 'd cry because she wanted to play .
But you 'd say : No , Sabina , you 're the salsa .
We 're monsters , Julian .
You wanted to fuck my sons ?
This is what you get if you mess with my family !
Bitches !
Sure this is it ?
That 's what the nut from the morgue said .
All units .
XDF 91 1 .
Acknowledge if you 're receiving .
And stop studying that file . You look ridiculous .
I 'll be right back . Don 't move .
These wolves will gobble you up .
I don 't care about life
I don 't care
About its suffering
Those who have nothing
Don 't even cry over love
They are happy
All the disappointments
Of a broken soul
Don 't hurt or harm you
They make you stronger
Life is so thankless
lt places you
On bitter paths
Of trouble
And suffering
But when the evening
Of our hard life comes
Our mother 's voice
is light , dear light
A long time ago , I used to sing on this line ...
to help pay for my son 's school .
Now he has a university degree ,
thanks to you .
To thank you in his name ,
I bring you these messages .
May you find God in the one I give you .
Here .
Maybe that is what you 're looking for .
" You are alive . "
I left something inside .
Did you get something ?
What are you doing ?
I brought you Gustavo .
Are you crazy ?
This is what we 're going to do .
- You don 't tell us what to do . - Shut up , Julian .
I 'm not eating a fag !
You 'll eat what I tell you to !
Stop it ! Stop it !
Who brought this guy ?
I did .
From now on , I decide what the family does .
Say that again !
- l 'm going to decide ... - Shut up !
Why do you hate me so much ?
Why have you always hated me ?
Why do you always push me away ?
Why did you make me like this ?
I did nothing . You were born that way .
That 's not true !
What do you want to kill these assholes ?
What are you waiting for ?
If I solve this case , I 'll be promoted
and I can forget about the shit on the streets .
You don 't want money ?
Look at this little morsel .
That 's for politicians or businessmen , no ?
You 're getting moralistic !
If you want us to follow you , you must be right .
It 's almost time . We have to begin the ritual .
- Leave me alone . - You okay ?
Leave me alone .
Where 's the faggot ?
Officer , they 're hunting me down !
They want to eat me !
They have a white car ...
All units , we have a 1 4 in progress .
All units ,
we have a 1 4 in progress in the project .
They caught your cannibals .
They 're in the Bicentennial project .
- ls the entrance on the avenue ? - Here , take a right !
HQ , this is unit 7 66 ...
We 're going to solve this shit on our own .
You 're going to waste them , aren 't you ?
To teach them a lesson .
Stop !
Easy now !
Put the weapon down , man .
You 're kidding !
Drop the gun !
I 'm police , damn it .
Careful , man !
Easy , easy !
Fuck !
What happened ?
- A cop got in . - What ?
We have to flee .
No ! We have to go on . It 's the only way to stop it .
We can 't keep going , Mom , we have to ...
lf we do the ritual , everything will be alright .
Trust me .
Let 's eat this one . It 's the only way to stop it .
- Mom . - We 're running out of time .
Look at me !
We have to go . We can 't do it now .
We can 't do it now .
Come on !
We have to escape from the roof .
We have to get to the roof . Come on !
We 'll go across the roof .
Come on !
They 're going to kill them . Come on !
It 's for the ritual .
Someone has to survive ...
for the ritual !
No ! Let her go !
Leave her alone !
All units report , send paramedics .
We have one survivor .
" You are alive ! "
" We Are What We Are "